- Are you going somewhere?
- I'm leaving.
When did you tell her?
This morning.
It had to happen. I guess.
She never wants
to see my face again.
Who pulled me out of
Addis in such a hurry?
I mean. who do I have to thank
after six years for
the 48-hour notice?
Coyote was arrested.
Shit.
Coyote knows of operations
currently ongoing in Ukraine.
Felix.
Rattlebox in L'viv.
Suspend
upcoming operations.
All covert activities
in Russia and Ukraine
may be compromised.
That why I'm back?
I want you to train
a new agent before we ship.
- Where to?
- Iran.
In at the deep end.
There's a shallow end?
- How are you settling in?
- Good.
Saw my daughter.
followed everywhere I go.
Phone's probably tapped.
You calling because of
the attack at the university?
- Yes.
-  I'm alive.
- I'm in London.
- Me too.
We should
have told him about
the backup tracker.
♪ "Love is Blindness"
by Jack White ♪
♪ Love is blindness ♪
♪ I don't want to see ♪
♪ Won't you wrap the night ♪
♪ Around me ♪
♪ Oh. my heart ♪
♪ Love is blindness ♪
♪ Blindness ♪
♪ I don't want to see ♪
♪ Won't you wrap the night ♪
♪ Around me. yeah ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ My love ♪
♪ Love is blindness ♪
♪ Oh. love is blindness ♪
♪ Oh. blow out the candle ♪
♪ Blindness ♪
When you
live undercover.
there's all these voices.
Loud voices. quiet voices.
♪ Dour. electronic music ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
This is everything
we could grab.
Great.
What is this stuff?
They're medical packs.
You know. we hand
them out to civilians
who come this way trying
to escape the front lines.
- You have kids?
- Two.
I got these. uh. great
coloring books and pens.
- Here. take a few. eh?
- Thanks.
Yeah.
Amber light.
Felix is amber.
- Is our cover blown?
- Negative.
Stand by.
Hey.
What does this mean?
Ukraine.
Forever.
Free.
♪ Somber music ♪
Back home. the
law would have me...
buried to my neck and stoned
to death for adultery.
When I left. I told myself
it was for the best.
I thought I could let you go.
Make it all easier for you.
For me.
I have to go.
Do you remember what
we said to each other
when we said goodbye?
Yes. I remember.
It was corny.
No. it wasn't.
Not at the time.
You and me. forever.
You and me.
Out of his league.
Not if he's paying for it.
4 a.m. It's a classic
hooker checkout.
Maybe they had a fight.
She does
not look angry.
She doesn't
look like a hooker.
Maybe she
has a plane to catch.
With no luggage?
Hey.
hey. hey. Wake up.
Here's your bugs. Breakfast.
I'm going home now.
Shower. then work.
via the Airlock.
♪ Inquisitive music ♪
Dr. Rachel Blake.
I'm here to see Foreign Service
Support Attaché Henry Ogletree.
Thanks.
Scenario one.
Coyote got drunk.
blew his cover.
They take him straight
from the police station
to a counterespionage unit.
Now the Belarusian
intelligence service has him.
He sobers up.
Says it's bullshit.
he was hammered.
What if while he was
hammered. he spilled his guts?
Evidence. contacts and...
Or worse. what if he did
but he doesn't remember?
Then they would've put him back
out in the field as a flytrap.
but they didn't.
they made him vanish.
Oh. great. So-so. uh.
Coyote... he got drunk
and he either did or didn't
do something he meant
or didn't mean to do that
he does or doesn't remember.
Yeah. I've had that
hangover. It's brutal.
How long was Coyote
at the Department
before being deployed?
Uh. 16 months.
So. 16
months of access
to classified operational
data. -
protocols. current covert ops.
I'm gonna puke.
Let's go over his legend.
Right. Yeah. so he lives alone.
uh. one-bedroom duplex bought
on a mortgage. no pets.
Works for a financial
consulting firm in Upper Minsk.
Uh. a lot of legit
activity. real clients.
A break and sweep
would totally stand up.
This guy has a real
life out there.
How many of his current
sources have we notified?
Uh. three. all on standby.
I contacted a fourth
who sounded spooked.
How spooked?
Look. it's a
precautionary measure.
- Is my cover blown?
- No. no. no.
not at all. you're safe.
It's Alexei Orekhov.
34 years old.
Manages a trucking
company linked
to Russian mercenary groups.
So why are we stopping?
- You don't want to tell me.
- It's protocol.
Protocol.
Yeah. it's protocol.
- It's protocol.
- Protocol.
Proto... Protocol.
You know who I work
with. One false move.
they cut my eyes out
and leave me in a ditch.
- How the fuck...
- All right.
We need to exfiltrate him now.
That'll be expensive.
Game it out. I'll talk to Henry.
You really think
he's that unstable?
Nope. I think we can use him.
So. uh...
he broke three trackers.
spent the night in a hotel
and in the morning.
gave you the slip.
Anything else?
- He bought us Danish.
- They were amazing.
Was he alone?
Hard to say.
People come in and out.
It's a hotel.
I know what a hotel is.
Our brief was to make sure
no one tails or IDs him. Okay?
If you want more. this
becomes surveillance.
And then you get everything.
Who he fucks. how many times.
does she like it in the ass.
Henry.
Hey. guys. Got a minute?
Yeah.
See you around.
What's up?
I think I found a wooden duck.
Every night. put all
documents in the shredder
or in this safe.
Your desk must be clear
and your trash empty.
We clean our own offices.
Codes here. Door.
safe. telephone.
You're familiar
with "need to know"?
I worked at Langley
for 16 years.
Now you're in the field.
We run non-official cover agents
from this floor. "Need
to know" is sacred.
Like professional
confidentiality.
Like classified intelligence.
Doctors get sued. not
executed for treason.
No one's been executed for
treason since the Civil War.
A-An exfil is a hundred grand.
I already got the FD up my ass.
A source is out there. on tilt.
We need to bring him
in. Spend the money.
You slept at a hotel last night.
Sea Containers. South Bank.
Don't change the subject.
Alone?
What is this. fatherly concern?
I'm not that old.
Why'd you shake your
protection team?
I'm training them.
Someone has to.
You know. post-mission disorder
- is...
- Is that a Joy Division album?
Henry.
Coyote's cell phone is
still at the station.
No one saw him leave.
Maybe he fucked up.
Or maybe he and
anyone he recruited
is a Russian double agent.
Spend the money.
Dr. Blake is here.
Right.
Dr. Blake. Welcome
to sunny old London.
This is NOC Case Officer
Martian. Dr. Blake
is over from our psych
department at Langley.
here to evaluate mental
health across the Department.
Sure you are.
Psychological well-being
is an agency-wide priority.
I'm here to observe.
lend an ear.
After one or two days. people
forget I'm even in the room.
Considering what we do here.
that's genuinely terrifying.
Can I show you something?
I'm leaving the service.
What?
I thought they
gave you a mission.
They did.
Long deployment
abroad. but I can't go.
Why not?
My boyfriend.
Oh. fuck him. This
is your career.
If I go. it'll destroy us.
Yeah. well.
he'll adapt. Danny.
Listen to me.
This is what you've worked for.
- It's who you are.
- I thought so. too.
♪ And what is wrong.
give me a sign... ♪
Guess not.
♪ What is love? ♪
She's here.
How were the farewells?
Uh. my colleagues
think I'm nuts.
Ex-colleagues.
I'm a tradwife to my
imaginary boyfriend.
Good job.
Been to Israel?
2018. I attended a sustainable
development conference
as part of my
engineering degree.
Iranian
intelligence films
all arrivals at Tel Aviv. Ben?
Uh. yeah. we're up in that
server. I can make it disappear.
Protocol.
Proto... Protocol.
You know who I work with.
One false move.
they cut my eyes out
and leave me in a ditch. I
demand to be exfiltrated.
If you won't do it.
I will do it my...
What's his panic level?
Critical. we find
a plausible reason
to yank him from the field.
Not critical. I
tell him go home.
take a bath. clear his head.
If you're wrong.
he risks arrest.
Execution.
Call it.
Dr. Blake?
Imagine you took
a routine checkup.
and when you call for the
results. the doctor says.
"I need more tests. Don't worry.
It's nothing. But whatever
you do. don't travel."
You live in West Africa.
There's an Ebola outbreak.
What would you do?
I'll get you the cash.
Take her with you.
Mr. Orekhov. I've
been trying to reach you.
Where have you been?
Who is this?
We spoke earlier about
arranging your travel.
Attention.
passengers flying to New York.
John F. Kennedy.
boarding will begin shortly...
Alexei. where are you?
I don't need you. Too slow.
Shit!
♪ Pulsing music ♪
- Blair!
- What?
Blair. he's already
at the airport.
Come on.
So. mental health.
What exactly is
healthy in this job?
Ever met anyone in the DO
who's tip-top in the pink?
If you have.
I hope you shitcanned them
for being a psychopath.
I'm a clinical psychologist.
I don't "shitcan" anyone.
I watch. evaluate.
So you're evaluating
me right now?
You check your rearview
mirrors every five seconds.
It's excessive.
Implies a lot.
You also register who's
driving any passing vehicle.
who else is in the vehicle.
make and color and where
the vehicle is registered.
Doesn't everyone?
Henry.
Orekhov's
at Minsk National
about to board a flight to
Istanbul connecting to JFK.
Fuck.
Okay.
How long till his flight boards?
- 47 minutes.
- Which airline?
Ottoman
Skylines. OT284...
And OT320. Istanbul to JFK.
If he flies to the U.S.. it's
as good as a signed confession.
so we need a new flight
plan for him out of Minsk.
Something that stacks
up if Belarusian KGB
or Russian FSB start digging.
Okay. tell me everything you
know about this guy. Details.
- All right. he...
- Uh. Alexei Orekhov.
Born 1989 in Kalodzishchy.
- suburb east of Minsk.
- One of-one of two boys.
Dad. farm worker.
died lung cancer in...
Uh. 1995. moved
to Minsk. age 18.
- Job in an auto plant.
- '95.
He was a truck driver
- placed by...
- He isn't a truck driver.
- He just runs the company.
- Was a truck driver.
Plays five-a-side soccer.
takes his mother to the
Sacred Heart Catholic Church
once a month and Christmas.
He's had
five girlfriends.
longest relationship. a year.
His brother moved to Gdansk.
He's a union dock worker.
A year ago. he was
diagnosed with...
- Lymphatic cancer.
- L... lymphatic cancer. which
- is presently in remission.
- Stop.
That's it. Gdansk.
Call
Orekhov. Tell him
he's on the next flight
to Gdansk. So are we.
What's going on? I thought
we were going to Vilnius.
Vilnius is OBE.
"Overtaken by events."
Don't fuck this up.
♪ suspenseful music ♪
- Alexei.
- Owen.
My friend. too late. I
am gone. I am on a flight
- in five minutes.
- Listen. Alexei.
We cancelled your ticket
and we deleted any record
of you buying a flight to JFK.
You will be stopped at the gate.
- Motherfucker.
- So. you need to listen
- to me. Alexei.
- I swear to God. if I meet you.
- I'm going to fucking kill you.
- Listen. Alexei.
- Alexei. you need - I'm
going to fucking kill you!
- To listen to me...
- Listen. Alexei.
Walk to the Air Poland desk.
There is a ticket in your
name on the 13:20 to Gdansk.
- I don't trust you.
- You're visiting your brother
in the hospital
there. His cancer?
- Oh.
- But right now...
Right now.
you're putting your
mother. your brother
and everyone you know in danger.
Starting with you.
Make the right
move here. Alexei.
- Jump wrong. - No.
- I can't help you.
- Wait. Hey.
- No one can.
- Wait...
- What the fuck?! I had
that. - I know you had it.
- By the way.
- I know you had it.
- Why'd you hang up?
- I don't know.
I just did it. I just
did it for emphasis
- or something.
- Emphasis? What?
- Well. did he agree?
- What do you mean?
Did he agree to
get on the flight?
Because it didn't sound
like he agreed to anything.
- The conversation was over.
- The conversation is over
when he agrees to get
on the fucking plane!
Yeah. well. my gut is
he'll be on the plane.
Your gut?
This is intelligence. Not Reno.
Orekhov
boarded the plane to Gdansk.
Nice catch.
And the
greeting party?
In position.
Go get it done.
Dmitri Orekhov?
Oh. Dmitri?
Excuse me. sir.
You speak English?
- Dmitri Orekhov?
- A little. Sure.
Dr. Tom Vincent.
I'm an American military doctor
attached to the
Embassy in Warsaw.
This is my colleague. Dr. Brown.
We're here about your brother.
- What about him? What's wrong?
- Russian counterespionage
thinks he's been
working for the CIA.
The U.S. consulate
there alerted us.
He may be charged with treason.
- What did he do?
- Nothing.
But he got scared and
skipped the country.
They think Alex is spy?
He can't
even tie shoes.
We just want to help him
make it out of this safely.
What can I do?
Check yourself into a hospital.
- Why?
- Alexei told his boss at work
he was coming to Poland to visit
his brother. who has cancer.
So. you want me to
pretend it came back?
Did you actually have cancer?
One year ago.
I'm under remission.
How come we didn't know
about this. Dr. Brown?
Uh. I thought...
We didn't have access
to any medical records.
It's just for a few days
till we make sure
your brother's safe.
Just few days.
Please don't put me
on the spot like that.
I am here to observe.
I wanted you to feel it.
What it's like
being someone else.
That was for five
seconds. not six years.
If we're quick. we'll make the
last flight back to London.
What about Orekhov?
Aren't you gonna be
there when he lands?
Orekhov won't make it
out of the airport.
♪ Intense music ♪
Welcome to Poland.
Take this car.
Where are you going?
Stop the car.
Stop the car. let me out.
Hey! Stop the fucking car!
Let me out!
Fuck you! Fuck.
JSOC called.
Oh?
The fuck is wrong
with you. Henry?
- Listen...
- Yeah.
Asking your brother-in-law
about a classified
op by code name...
a code name you weren't
even supposed to know...
you didn't think that
was gonna come back?
On the contrary.
I hoped it would.
Why?
I wanted to know
if he's exposed.
He's on a black
op in a war zone.
Nothing operational was shared.
I know nothing about Felix.
All I had was a name.
You want to know something?
I believe you.
Want to know why?
Because I. Henry.
am station chief.
and even I don't
know what Felix is.
Which means that Felix.
is the very. very heaviest
of heavy. heavy shit.
and nobody... not
you. not I. no one...
would ever mention.
Ever.
Hey.
All right. How much
is it gonna cost me?
Uh. 50 grand. tops.
Twenty K for the transfer.
three agents. company jet.
Two agents for the mission.
equipment. etcetera.
Twenty for the
interrogation. ten for post.
Yeah. What are the risks?
Apart from the fifty grand
and losing Orekhov forever?
But the upside?
If he is a double.
Coyote is. too.
Can you do it for forty?
- Can't do it for forty.
- Forty-five.
Forty-eight.
What is this.
a Turkish bazaar?
- Hmm.
- All right.
let me explain how budgetary
allocations are made
within the U.S. government
departments. Henry.
The station chief submits
a quarterly request
to the overseas accounts
committee in Langley.
spearheaded by
a Mrs. Martina-Louise Brooks.
Now. Mrs. Brooks
does not like me.
I'd go as far as to say
that Mrs. Brooks does not
believe in Europe as a concept.
Forty-seven.
Sold.
Begin.
Hi.
So. we are here
to take your lunch orders.
What is going to be?
Waffles or pizza?
Cheeseburgers or hot dogs?
Coca-Cola or McDonald's?
Tupac or Biggie?
Bill or Hillary?
Beyoncé or Taylor Swift?
How much can we hurt him?
- What's the ceiling?
- Low to medium.
He's in Russia. They
don't play nice.
- It's a wooden duck.
- ♪ Born ♪
- ♪ In the USA ♪
- I'm just saying.
♪ I'm
a long gone daddy ♪
♪ In the USA now ♪
♪ Born in the USA ♪
♪Born in the USA ♪
♪ I'm a long gone
daddy in the... ♪
Is a doctor on standby?
Can be.
Let him cook.
- Put him in the dark.
- ♪ Born in the USA ♪
♪ I'm a cool ♪
♪ Daddy in the USA ♪
♪ Dancing in the dark ♪
Sorry.
Wooden duck?
Squeeze a wooden duck.
it doesn't quack.
If this guy works
for the Russians.
soon as he's had
enough. he'll quack.
"Guys. time-out.
Fuck America. I'm on your team."
Doesn't quack. we're good.
"Good." meaning?
He's alive next week and
so are lots of others.
And if he does quack?
Then we're fucked.
♪ intriguing music playing ♪
Negative.
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm?
Vodka?
Wait.
Did I hear... What's he saying?
"I report to Moscow."
Fuck.
"I work for...
the Americans and
the Russians."
"I report...
to Drezin in the FSB."
Go get Bosko. Drezin.
do we know him?
No. I'm on it.
What section does
Drezin work for?
Counterespionage?
Military security?
Says he doesn't know. Well?
No Drezin.
Say he's bullshitting.
He's saying it's true.
Who recruited him?
Ivanov.
Verify Ivanov.
Ivanov is Smith.
- It's like Smith in the U.S.
- Verify.
Where's his dead drop?
A locker at Minsk
railway station.
What locker number?
He can't remember.
What's happening?
He's quacking.
What was the last
intel he delivered
to the Americans?
♪ ominous music ♪
Transport manifests
and container
inventories from Moscow
into Belarus. on
to Eastern Ukraine.
Medical supplies
for clinics there.
Call JSOC.
I need time.
Pressure what he's
saying. cross-check.
Your brother-in-law's
on the ground out there.
We move when we're
sure. I need time.
I need to tell JSOC what we know
when we know it.
God knows they hate
us enough already.
♪ Pulsing music ♪
What's up?
Emergency abort signal.
What about our target?
It's not your target anymore.
Leave nothing behind.
We're not coming back.
What the hell happened?
Something killed the mission.
We'll find out more
when it's safe.
This Ivanov
he says he worked
for... exist or not?
Maybe
it's a code name.
If he's genuine. he
wouldn't know his real name.
What do we do?
Ask if he knows Ivanov's rank.
Colonel.
Ask if he's heard of
Colonel Sergei Mezakov.
That a pitfall?
And he didn't jump in. Shit.
How and when were you paid?
Into what account?
Cash. Russian rubles.
He never banked it.
♪ suspenseful music ♪
Fuck me.
They must have crossed
the river and taken
the power station last night.
What do you want me to do?
Well. our options
here are limited.
When I say go.
punch right through.
Fuck. fuck. fuck. fuck. fuck me.
JSOC report.
I got three
operators from Felix.
two-man Ukrainian
special forces sniper team.
I got one U.S. Delta operator.
They got the orders to abort
too late to get out clean.
They're engaging Russian forces.
SOG has 'em on satellite
and will report.
I'm sorry. Henry.
♪ Tense music ♪
Did we lose them?
Can't fucking see.
Stop!
Push it!
We got to move.
Take it. Remy?
All right. this is
what we're gonna do.
You boys take cover
behind those diggers.
maybe cause a diversion.
I'll go left flank.
I'll get up behind them.
Copy?
Copy that.
You good?
Yeah.
All right.
♪ intense music ♪
We got him!
Wrap it up. brief him.
get him a meal and a bed.
What's so funny?
Uh. are you a fan of
Russian literature?
No. I'm more of a
Conan Doyle guy.
What the fuck are
you talking about?
Well. this isn't any three-pipe
problem for Sherlock Holmes.
Those names aren't
in Orekhov's network.
How do you know?
Because they're
in War and Peace.
Your name is
Daniela Moreno Acosta.
You were born in Seville. raised
in Sanlúcar de Barrameda. Spain.
You visited cousins
in New York a lot.
which explains your
love of the Knicks
and your excellent English.
I'll be your postman.
Martian will oversee
your deployment.
Who's this?
Professor Reza Mortazevi.
Visiting professor of seismology
at the London
School of Sciences.
You're being sent to Tehran
to identify Iranian
nuclear engineers.
Professor Mortazevi
runs an exchange program
between the London
School of Sciences
and the University
College of Tehran.
He comes to London every
two years to lecture
at the Institute of Geophysics.
Your job is to be hired there.
Impress him.
Convince him you're the
candidate for his program.
Then you'll be traveling to Iran
with a certified
Iranian official.
100% copper-bottomed.
watertight cover.
How do I get a research job at
the Institute of Geophysics?
That's your problem.
But what if I don't make it in?
Then go home.
Figure out something else
to do with your life.
♪ Contemplative music ♪
Follow me.
Here.
There's a cost for
doing this work.
A price.
Are you sure you want to pay it?
Uh. how's it going?
It's going.
Okay. uh.
yeah. so. Sami Zahir.
uh. entered from Addis.
uh. February 25th
on a six-month
professional visa.
Uh. she made two
round trips back
and she enrolled with the. um.
the Royal College
of World Heritage.
I mean. she's clean.
She checks out. Looks legit.
- You're certain?
- Uh. yeah.
Yeah. she's. uh. she's
staying in a room in Raffles.
- Under her real name.
- Did you scrape her phone?
No. no. it's encrypted.
and I couldn't see in.
I-I mean. I can. if you want.
but. um. it'll take longer.
and I'd. uh. I-I'd need
a mission number to
log for the time.
Don't ever take a file
out of the office again
or you're fired.
I'm not talking about
the hardships it presents.
I'm talking about what
it costs a human being
to abandon their identity.
To spend however many
days. weeks. or years
they have left alive
in another skin.
Hi.
It's Daniela.
Acosta.
Thank you.
Uh. champagne. please.
Professor. I'd like
to introduce you to someone.
You have
to ask yourself
is it worth it?
Do I really want
to pay the price?
Professor Wartenburg?
Excuse me. Professor Wartenburg?
- Hello.
- Hi.
I'm Daniela.
I just wanted to
introduce myself
and let you know that
I read your paper.
- Oh?
- Your most recent paper.
What is the price?
I don't see any Ms. Zahir
signed in for this
evening's lecture.
Check the register. third floor.
Thank you.
The price is surviving
totally alone.
Forever.
[narrator on screen
Artifacts that had survived
for thousands of years
obliterated in a moment
at Palmyra...
and the Mosul Museum.
The destruction was motivated
less by religious dogma
and more to send a
message to the West.
I find these images
incredibly painful.
Rockets and pickaxes
destroying the statue...
And that can never be replaced.
Right. uh...
let's break and meet
back in 15 minutes
to discuss the film.
- Uh. Professor?
- Mm?
I was just wondering.
could you help me...
Yeah. sure.
Just give me second.
I'll be right back with that.
- Hi.
- Yeah?
I'm looking for someone
attending your conference.
Dr. Samia Zahir?
Ah. Dr. Zahir.
Yes. uh. she enrolled.
Tell her I said hi.
She's not been back
since the first day.
She did well to enroll so that
UNESCO could validate her visa.
Hope she's enjoying London.
♪ Quiet. dramatic music ♪
So. she wasn't there?
She never was.
I could have gone back.
sat down with Henry
and said. "Guess
what. I fucked up."
But when you live undercover.
there's all these voices.
Loud voices. quiet voices.
The quietest of all
is always there.
It says the same
thing over and over.
"I can do this."
"I can do anything."
You know what the voice is?
It's hope.
That's the thing
about this game.
If you're hoping... if
you hope anything...
ever. at any time...
it's too late.
♪ Mysterious music ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm